# **SWETA AGARWAL**

Email: agarwalsweta434@gmail.com | Phone: 7004334144 | LinkedIn

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Account and Social Media Manager with an experience of 4+ years in the Advertising and Branding agency. Handled the brands LAKME, Planet Fashion, Isak Fragrances, Bombay Sweets, Event Industries, HORECA, Interiors, Clothing, Real Estate, Jewelry, Cinemas. Strong Media and Advertising Professional with a Masters Degree specialized in Advertising and Marketing Communication from NIHT Kolkata.

#### **WORK HISTORY**

# ACCOUNT AND SOCIAL MEDIA EXECUTIVE AT WEB LUMENS [FEBRUARY 2020 - PRESENT] [ KOLKATA ]

- Working with more than 10+ industries for their social media projects engaged highly in FMCG and events industry.
- Manages a **team of 5+ members** and assists them in the smooth functioning of their tasks.
- Coordinates with clients for decision making and maintains peaceful client relations.
- Accountable for Online Reputation Management (ORM) for the brands to maintain respective brand tones.
- Experienced in Market Research and Marketing collaborations and successfully onboarded and collaborated with 10+ brands and influencers online.
- Plans required product photoshoots and helps in brand building.
- Strategize monthly and yearly project timelines to carry out successful social media and marketing campaigns.

#### SOCIAL MEDIA INTERN AT THE SOCIAL ERA [ DECEMBER 2019 – JANUARY 2020] [ MUMBAI ]

- Handled entire social media platforms and worked on brand briefs, reports and analysis.
- Planned monthly social media calendar and strategies.
- Planned Ad campaigns plus day-to-day account activities.

## SOCIAL MEDIA INTERN AT LAKME [SEPTEMBER 2019 - OCTOBER 2019] [KOLKATA]

- Handled the Kolkata based social media accounts.
- Build campaigns and worked on brand briefs.
- Helped in building the team and developing the business.
- Curated ideas, content plus day-to-day account activities.

#### **SKILLS**

- **Digital Marketing** Social Media Marketing, Facebook Ads Manager, Meta Business Suite, Google Adwords
- Data Analysis MS Excel, Google Sheets
- Graphic Design Canva
- Soft Skills Creativity, Project Management, Business Communication, Team Management, Leadership, Adaptibility

## **ACADEMIC QUALIFICATION**

- Diploma Degree in Digital Marketing ( 1 Year ) NIHT Kolkata 2018 2019
- Bachelors in Commerce (Honors) Shri Shikshayatan College, Kolkata 2016 2019

#### **EXTRACURRICULARS AND ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Certified as the Most Active Social Media Partner by LAKME.
- Awarded for Best Employee and Best Intern of the month at Web Lumens.
- Received Certificate of Appreciation for outstanding academic performance at school in 2016.

## **CERTIFICATIONS AND TRAININGS**

- Diploma Degree in Digital Marketing (1 Year) NIHT Kolkata 2018 2019
- Google Ads Certification 2019
- Facebook Ads Certification 2019